Good morning.
It is half past seven in the morning and I woke up to go to the bathroom.
But check, I don't want to go back.
I don't want to sleep again.
I don't want to fall asleep.
I can not.
Now I'm going to take a walk instead.
It doesn't blow.
It is completely still.
The sun is shining, it's hot.
Everyone is asleep.
Only me is awake throughout the campsite.
We take a walk together.
One has woken up and will walk with his dog.
She should rest the dog.
We are two who are awake.
There is a flagpole, two flagpoles and you can see that the flags are completely still.
It doesn't blow at all.
The campsite is called Herta Camping.
You can look at the map on Gotland, where it is located.
Drive slowly.
Look what amazing flowers.
Giant.
Superfine on both sides.
Here is my shadow.
There is the sea.
The campsite is very close to the beach.
Check this out.
It's a cows.
Several cows.
A kiss.
Several kisses.
What do they do?
That kiss is itching.
It scratches the forehead.
Those stand and eat something.
Completely still.
This road is a dirt road.
I walk on the dirt road.
Over there is the sea.
The sea is also completely still because it does not blow.
So this is a pasture.
A cowhage for cows.
And this is a horse pasture.
A cowhage and a horse pasture.
This horse stands and eats.
It is said that the horse grazes.
And that horse is sleeping.
It looks like that.
We continue forward to the beach.
Just on the beach there are some houses.
These houses are very small.
A small house.
Many small houses.
They are not real.
I think it's cottages.
That climbs on the walls.
Here is a small scene.
You can do different events.
Old stones.
And here there is also the roof left.
The roof is made of small, small stones.
A sheep.
So there are large stone sheep in the square and everywhere.
In Stockholm it is lion and on Gotland it is sheep.
There is a wall around Visbystaden.
This is a wall.
This is a tower.
This is a gate.
The wall goes around Visby.
You can walk here.
Inside the wall is the old town.
Outside the wall, it is the new city maybe.